British Columbia Honey Producers Association fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Association records, 1943 - 2005; F-147-1; 2.24 m of textual records 1 audio cassette
  - Newsletters, 1968 - 2005; F-147-1-4; 28.5 cm of textual records
    - BEE CEE BEES, 1968; F-147-1-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-4)
      Open
    - BCHPA Newsletter, 1979 - 1980; F-147-1-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 147-4)
    - BCHPA Newsletter, 1981; F-147-1-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 147-4)
    - BCHPA Newsletter, 1982; F-147-1-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 147-5)
    - BCHPA Newsletter, 1983; F-147-1-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 147-5)
    - BCHPA Newsletter, 1984; F-147-1-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 147-5)
    - BeesCene, 1985; F-147-1-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 147-5)
    - BeesCene, 1986; F-147-1-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 147-5)
    - BeesCene, 1987; F-147-1-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 147-5)
    - BeesCene, 1988; F-147-1-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 147-5)
    - BeesCene, 1989; F-147-1-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 147-5)
    - BeesCene, 1990; F-147-1-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 147-5)
    - BeesCene, 1991; F-147-1-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 147-5)
    - BeesCene, 1992; F-147-1-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 147-5)
    - BeesCene, 1993; F-147-1-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 147-5)
    - BeesCene, 1994; F-147-1-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 147-5)
    - BeesCene, 1995; F-147-1-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 147-6)
    - BeesCene, 1996; F-147-1-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 147-6)
    - BeesCene, 1997; F-147-1-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 147-6)
    - BeesCene, 1998; F-147-1-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 147-6)
    - BeesCene, 1999; F-147-1-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 147-6)
    - BeesCene, 2000; F-147-1-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 147-6)
    - Bee sCene (vol. 3, no. 4), 1987; F-147-1-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 147-21)
    - BeesCene (vol. 17, nos. 1-4), 2001; F-147-1-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 147-25)
    - BeesCene (vol. 18, nos. 1-4), 2002; F-147-1-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 147-25)
    - BeesCene (vol. 19, nos. 1, 3, 4), 2003; F-147-1-4-0-26 (Archival box - standard 147-25)
    - BeesCene (vol. 20, nos. 1-4), 2004; F-147-1-4-0-27 (Archival box - standard 147-25)
    - BeesCene (vol. 21, nos. 1-4), 2005; F-147-1-4-0-28 (Archival box - standard 147-25)
  - Organization records, 1951 - 1999; F-147-1-5; 10 cm of textual records; See sub-series F-147-1-7 for records relating to the administration of BCHPA membership.
    Sub-series comprises records relating to the governance and structure of the BCHPA as an organization. Activities documented include revisions to the constitution and by-laws, development of policies and procedures, and awarding of honorary life-memberships. Records include constitution and by-laws, correspondence, reports, annotated drafts, procedures, and policy manuals.
    - Constitution and by-laws, 1953 - 1987; F-147-1-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-6)
    - Constitution revision, 1951 - 1981; F-147-1-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 147-6)
    - Procedures and history, 1966 - 1990; F-147-1-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 147-6)
    - New by-laws, 1986 - 1988; F-147-1-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 147-6)
    - Life members, 1987; F-147-1-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 147-6)
    - BC Commercial Beekeepers Association: constitution and by-laws, 1965 - 1966; F-147-1-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 147-12)
      British Columbia Commercial Beekeepers Association; Textual records
    - BCHPA: constitution and by-laws, 1956; F-147-1-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 147-12)
    - BCHPA: constitution and by-laws, 1961; F-147-1-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 147-12)
    - BCHPA: constitution and by-laws, 1970; F-147-1-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 147-12)
    - BCHPA: constitution and by-laws, 1972; F-147-1-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 147-12)
    - BCHPA: constitution and by-laws, convention procedures, 1975 - 1999; F-147-1-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 147-21)
    - Convention procedures - use, revisions, 1993 - 1995; F-147-1-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 147-21)
  - Projects and activities files, 1950 - 1998; F-147-1-6; 31 cm of textual records 1 audio cassette
    Sub-series comprises records relating to projects and activities undertaken by the BCHPA according to its mandate and functions. Activities documented include the work of the Bee Forage Committee and the Education Committee; participation in educational programs, including the Malaspina College Apiculture program and a Tracheal Mite seminar; reports to the provincial Minister; promotions and exhibits, including participation in the Granville Island Public Market; production of a honey cookbook; advocacy and projects in formal and informal partnership with the Ministry of Agriculture, including the BC Honeybee Stock Improvement Project and revisions to the Bee Act; and the early exploration of the possibility of commercial production of mead in BC. Records include correspondence, briefs and reports, drafts, minutes, brochures, and course-related material.
    Textual records; Sound recordings
    - Information brochures, 1972 - 1989; F-147-1-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-6)
    - Bee Forage Committee, 1980 - 1983; F-147-1-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 147-6)
    - Brief to the Minister of Agriculture and Food, 1982 - 1983; F-147-1-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 147-6)
    - Education Committee, 1982 - 1983; F-147-1-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 147-6)
    - Malaspina College Apiculture Program, 1982 - 1985; F-147-1-6-0-5 (Archival box - small 147-7)
    - Granville Island Public Market, 1983 - 1984; F-147-1-6-0-6 (Archival box - small 147-7)
    - Honey promotion T-shirts, hats and pins, 1983 - 1986; F-147-1-6-0-7 (Archival box - small 147-7)
    - Canadian honey cookbook, 1984; F-147-1-6-0-8 (Archival box - small 147-7)
    - Agri-Food Regional Development Subsidiary Agreement (ARDSA) proposal, 1986; F-147-1-6-0-9 (Archival box - small 147-7)
    - Proposals, briefs, reports, 1987; F-147-1-6-0-10 (Archival box - small 147-7)
    - Tracheal Mite seminar, 1990; F-147-1-6-0-11 (Archival box - small 147-7)
    - Border closure, 1993; F-147-1-6-0-12 (Archival box - small 147-7)
    - Correspondence regarding mead and exploration of possibility of commercial production in BC - Harvey Boone, 1950 - 1966; F-147-1-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 147-21)
      Boone, Harvey; Textual records
    - BC Honeybee Stock Improvement Project and Queen Rearing Project - minutes, reports, proposals, and supporting documentation, vol. 1, 1977 - [ca. 1983]; F-147-1-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 147-21)
    - BC Honeybee Stock Improvement Project and Queen Rearing Project - minutes, reports, proposals, and supporting documentation, vol. 2, 1977 - [ca. 1983]; F-147-1-6-0-15 (Archival box - standard 147-22)
    - BCHPA PNE Honey Committee and shows, 1978 - 1983; F-147-1-6-0-16 (Archival box - standard 147-22)
      Pacific National Exhibition; Textual records
    - BC Federation of Beekeepers, 1984 - 1985; F-147-1-6-0-17 (Archival box - standard 147-22)
      British Columbia Federation of Beekeepers; Textual records
    - Beekeeping in British Columbia: A Strategic Plan for..., 1987; F-147-1-6-0-18 (Archival box - standard 147-22)
    - Bee Act Committee - input on Act revisions, vol. 1, 1989 - 1991; F-147-1-6-0-19 (Archival box - standard 147-22)
    - Bee Act Committee - input on Act revisions, vol. 2, 1989 - 1991; F-147-1-6-0-20 (Archival box - standard 147-22)
      - Guest Provincial Apiarist: Paul van Westendorp, February 21, 1991; F-147-1-6-0-20-1; 1 audio cassette 2 .wav files (Audio cassette OBJ-4625)
        Item is a recording of a meeting of the Shuswap Beekeepers Association held at Salmon Arm, BC on February 21, 1991. The purpose of the meeting was to discuss nine questions posed to all BCHPA Divisions, Associations, and other BC beekeepers by the BCHPA Bee Act Committee. The Committee was struck as an informal group to assist in the formulation and direction of revisions to be applied to the BC Bee Act by the Ministry. The recording begins mid-discussion at the start of side 1. In addition to input from Paul van Westendorp, the BC Provincial Apiarist, questions and comments arise from the members as the discussion around the nine questions ensues. Questions and concerns raised by the audience are not always fully clear, but van Westendorp's responses are. There is also the occasional sound of movement and disruption to the recording mic. The meeting adjourns halfway through side 1, and the recording cuts to a presentation by van Westendorp on tracheal mites and the BC Policy on Movement of Bees as they pertain to the question of quarantine areas, a question posed by the Bee Act Committee. Van Westendorp takes questions from the audience, and his talk continues onto side 2. The talk comes to a close approximately 2 minutes before the end of the second side. A summary of the Association's decisions on the nine questions are included on the file.
        Van Westendorp, Paul; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
        The audio cassette is a 100-minute tape
        - OBJ-4625_SideA.wav
        - OBJ-4625_SideB.wav
    - Bee Act revisions, 1990 - 1994; F-147-1-6-0-21 (Archival box - standard 147-22)
    - Pollination standards and bee movement, 1991 - 1996; F-147-1-6-0-22 (Archival box - standard 147-22)
    - Mites, 1991 - 1998; F-147-1-6-0-23 (Archival box - standard 147-22)
    - All Industry Committee, 1992; F-147-1-6-0-24 (Archival box - standard 147-22)
    - Marketing, 1993; F-147-1-6-0-25 (Archival box - standard 147-22)
    - Apiculture Program and BCHPA - strategic planning, 1993 - 1996; F-147-1-6-0-26 (Archival box - standard 147-22)
    - Apiary Branch - Policy on the Movement of Bees and other issues, 1993 - 1997; F-147-1-6-0-27 (Archival box - standard 147-23)
    - Agriculture enhancement legislation input, Ministry funding cut concerns, 1995; F-147-1-6-0-28 (Archival box - standard 147-23)
  - Membership records, [ca. 1985] - 2002; F-147-1-7; 2 cm of textual records; Files pertaining to membership are also found in the Organization Records sub-series (F-147-1-5) and Subject Files series (F-147-8).
    Sub-series comprises records relating to the administration of BCHPA membership. Records include lists, directories, forms, and correspondence.
    - BCHPA membership lists, division directory, and application form, [ca. 1985], 1997 - 2002; F-147-1-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-23)
    - Membership - lists, directories, member insurance correspondence, and application form, 1993 - 1997; F-147-1-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 147-23)
  - Boone Hodgson Wilkinson Trust Fund records, 1965 - 2004; F-147-1-8; 16 cm of textual records; Files pertaining to the BHW Trust Fund are also found in the Financial Records sub-series (F-147-1-2) and the Subject Files series (F-147-8).
    Sub-series comprises records relating to the history, development, and administration of the Boone Hodgson Wilkinson Trust Fund. The BHW Trust Fund was established by BC Provincial Apiarist John Corner at the BCHPA's annual general meeting in 1965. The aim of the Fund was to provide opportunities for the study of apiculture at BC post-secondary institutions. The Trust was named for Harvey Boone, Percy Hodgson, and George Wilkinson, who had each contributed significantly to apiculture and beekeepers in BC. All three men, along with Leo Fuhr of Vernon, were appointed by BCHPA members as the first trustees of the Fund. The aims of the BHW Trust Fund have ultimately grown to include not only the support of apiculture education, but research as well. Records include correspondence, proposals, reports, financial statements, and supporting documents.
    - Minutes of Annual Meeting BCHPA Oct 1965 with cover letter from John Corner to Harvey Boone, 1965 - 1966; F-147-1-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-23)
    - Correspondence, [ca. 1965 - 1970]; F-147-1-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 147-23)
    - BHW Fund inception and administration records, 1966, 1979 - 1999; F-147-1-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 147-23)
    - Financial statements, 1968 - 1997; F-147-1-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 147-23)
    - BHW founder information, obituaries - Boone and Wilkinson, 1969, 1984; F-147-1-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 147-23)
    - Correspondence, 1971 - 1981; F-147-1-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 147-23)
    - Correspondence, 1978 - 1989; F-147-1-8-0-7 (Archival box - standard 147-23)
    - Constitution, bylaws - amendments, 1983, 2001 - 2003; F-147-1-8-0-8 (Archival box - standard 147-24)
    - Disbursements, 1984 - 2000; F-147-1-8-0-9 (Archival box - standard 147-24)
    - Research reports, 1990 - 1992; F-147-1-8-0-10 (Archival box - standard 147-24)
    - Projects completed, 1992 - 2000; F-147-1-8-0-11 (Archival box - standard 147-24)
    - Journal - financial statements, 1997 - 2003; F-147-1-8-0-12 (Archival box - standard 147-24)
    - Research proposals, 2001; F-147-1-8-0-13 (Archival box - standard 147-24)
    - Correspondence, 2001 - 2002; F-147-1-8-0-14 (Archival box - standard 147-24)
    - BHW reports - annual meetings and semi-annual meeting, 2001 - 2004; F-147-1-8-0-15 (Archival box - standard 147-24)
    - Research proposals, 2003 - 2004; F-147-1-8-0-16 (Archival box - standard 147-24)
    - Statement of activities, 2003 - 2004; F-147-1-8-0-17 (Archival box - standard 147-24)
- Greater Vancouver Division records, 1941 - 1954; F-147-2; 3 cm of textual records
  Series comprises records made or received by the Greater Vancouver Division of the BCHPA. The Greater Vancouver Division joined the Association in 1931, as the remnant of the former Beekeepers Association of British Columbia, originally founded in 1916 and from which the BCHPA split in 1920. Activities documented include Division meetings and management of Division finances. Records consist of minutes and a register of accounts book.
  - Financial records, 1941 - 1949; F-147-2-1; 1 cm of textual records
    Sub-series comprises records relating to the management of the Greater Vancouver Division's finances. Records consist of a register of accounts book.
    A file list is available.
    - Register of accounts - Greater Vancouver Division, 1941 - 1949; F-147-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - small 147-7)
  - Meeting minutes, 1947 - 1954; F-147-2-2; 1 cm of textual records
    Sub-series comprises minutes of the Greater Vancouver Division, including annual meetings and directors' meetings.
    - Greater Vancouver Division meetings, 1947 - 1954; F-147-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - small 147-7)
- Capital Region Division records, 1972 - 1994; F-147-3; 17 cm of textual records
  Series comprises records made or received by the Capital Region Division of the BCHPA. Activities documented include Division meetings, management of Division finances, and communications. Records consist of correspondence, financial statements, meeting minutes, and newsletters.
  Files are arranged chronologically. As a result of an accrual added in 2014 (accession 2012-001), an additional sub-series was created by the processing archivist to facilitate intellectual access to the documents: F-147-3-4 (Newsletters).
  - Correspondence, 1972 - 1982; F-147-3-1; 9 cm of textual records
    Sub-series comprises correspondence conducted by Division officers with members, provincial and federal government ministries and agencies, and with other bee-related organizations and individuals.
    - Capital Region division correspondence, 1972 - 1974; F-147-3-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-12)
    - Capital Region division correspondence, 1974 - 1975; F-147-3-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 147-12)
    - Capital Region division correspondence, 1975 - 1976; F-147-3-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 147-13)
    - Capital Region division correspondence, 1976 - 1977; F-147-3-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 147-13)
    - Capital Region division correspondence, 1977 - 1978; F-147-3-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 147-13)
    - Capital Region division correspondence, 1978; F-147-3-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 147-13)
    - Capital Region division correspondence, 1978 - 1979; F-147-3-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 147-13)
    - Capital Region division correspondence, 1978 - 1982; F-147-3-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 147-13)
  - Financial records, 1980 - 1984; F-147-3-2; 1 cm of textual records
    Sub-series comprises records relating to the management of the Capital Region Divison's financial resources. Records consist of financial statements, ledger pages, correspondence and other documents.
    - Capital Region division financial statements, 1980 - 1984; F-147-3-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-13)
  - Meeting minutes, 1974 - 1979; F-147-3-3; 4 cm of textual records
    Sub-series comprises minutes of the Capital Region Division, including annual meetings, executive committee meetings and general meetings.
    - Capital Region Division annual general meetings, 1975 - 1978; F-147-3-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-13)
    - Capital Region Division Executive Committee meetings, 1975 - 1979; F-147-3-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 147-13)
    - Capital Region Division general meetings, 1974 - 1979; F-147-3-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 147-13)
  - Newsletters, 1982 - 1994; F-147-3-4; 2 cm of textual records
    Sub-series comprises "Beeline," the newsletter of the Capital Region Division.
    - Beeline: Newsletter of the B.C. Honey Producers' Association Capital Region Division, 1982 - 1988; F-147-3-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-24)
    - Beeline: Newsletter of the B.C. Honey Producers' Association Capital Region Division, 1988 - 1994; F-147-3-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 147-24)
- BCHPA Chilliwack Division records, 1951 - 1988; F-147-4; 9 cm of textual records
  Series comprises records made or received by the Chilliwack Division of the BCHPA. Records consist of correspondence, meeting minutes, and newsletters.
  Files are arranged chronologically. As a result of an accrual added in 2014 (accession 2012-001), an additional sub-series was created by the processing archivist to facilitate intellectual access to the documents: F-147-4-3 (Newsletters).
  - Correspondence, 1979 - 1983; F-147-4-1; 1 cm of textual records
    - Chilliwack Division correspondence, 1979 - 1983; F-147-4-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-14)
  - Meeting minutes, 1951 - 1964; F-147-4-2; 7 cm of textual records
    Sub-series comprises minutes of the Chilliwack Division, including annual meetings and executive committee meetings.
    - Chilliwack Division annual meeting, 1951 - 1953; F-147-4-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-14)
    - Chilliwack Division annual meeting, 1956; F-147-4-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 147-14)
    - Chilliwack Division annual meeting, 1957; F-147-4-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 147-14)
    - Chilliwack Division annual meeting, 1958 - 1959; F-147-4-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 147-14)
    - Chilliwack Division annual meeting, 1960; F-147-4-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 147-14)
    - Chilliwack Division annual meeting, 1961; F-147-4-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 147-14)
    - Chilliwack Division annual meeting, 1961 - 1962; F-147-4-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 147-14)
    - Chilliwack Division annual meeting, 1963 - 1964; F-147-4-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 147-14)
    - Chilliwack Division Executive Committee meeting, 1953 - 1956; F-147-4-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 147-14)
  - Newsletters, 1988; F-147-4-3; 1 cm of textual records
    Sub-series comprises "Beeswack," the newsletter of the Chilliwack Division.
    - Beeswack: newsletter of the Chilliwack Division, B.C.H.P.A., 1988; F-147-4-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-24)
- BCHPA Fraser Valley division records, 1923 - 1988; F-147-5; 5 cm of textual records
  Series comprises records made or received by the Fraser Valley Division of the BCHPA. Records consist of correspondence, meeting minutes, and newsletters.
  Files are arranged chronologically. As a result of an accrual added in 2014 (accession 2012-001), an additional sub-series was created by the processing archivist to facilitate intellectual access to the documents: F-147-5-3 (Newsletters).
  - Correspondence, 1979 - 1982; F-147-5-1; 1 cm of textual records
    - Fraser Valley Division correspondence, 1979 - 1982; F-147-5-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-14)
  - Meeting minutes, 1923 - 1956; F-147-5-2; 3 cm of textual records
    Sub-series comprises minutes of the annual meetings of the Fraser Valley Division.
    - Fraser Valley Division annual meeting, 1923 - 1930; F-147-5-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-14)
    - Fraser Valley Division annual meeting, 1931 - 1940; F-147-5-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 147-14)
    - Fraser Valley Division annual meeting, 1941 - 1950; F-147-5-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 147-14)
    - Fraser Valley Division annual meeting, 1951 - 1956; F-147-5-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 147-14)
  - Newsletters, 1986 - 1988; F-147-5-3; 1 cm of textual records
    Sub-series comprises "The Fraser Valley Beekeeper," the newsletter of the Fraser Valley Division.
    - The Fraser Valley Beekeeper: newsletter of the Fraser Valley Division of the B.C.H.P.A., 1986 - 1988; F-147-5-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-24)
- BCHPA Vancouver Island division records, 1963 - 1970; F-147-6; 1 cm of textual records
  Series comprises records made or received by the Vancouver Island Division of the BCHPA. Records include minutes and notices.
  - Vancouver Island minutes / notices (infrequent), 1963 - 1970; F-147-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
- BC Commercial Beekeepers' Association records, 1962 - 1974; F-147-7; 8 cm of textual records
  Series comprises records made or received by the BC Commercial Beekeepers' Association. Records consist of correspondence and meeting minutes.
  British Columbia Commercial Beekeepers Association
  For related material, see the finding aid for the fonds of the Apiculture (Beekeeping) Collection / SFU Archives Collector (F-110)
  - Correspondence, 1963 - 1974; F-147-7-1; 1 cm of textual records
    Sub-series comprises correspondence conducted by Association officers with members, provincial and federal government ministries and agencies, and with other bee-related organizations and individuals.
    - BC Commercial Beekeepers' Association correspondence, 1963 - 1974; F-147-7-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
  - Meeting minutes, 1962 - 1972; F-147-7-2; 7 cm of textual records
    Sub-series comprises minutes of the semi-annual and annual meetings of the BC Commercial Beekeepers' Association.
    - BCCBA -- semi-annual meeting, 1962; F-147-7-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
    - BCCBA -- annual general meeting - Kamloops, 1964; F-147-7-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
    - BCCBA -- semi-annual meeting - Mission, 1964; F-147-7-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
    - BCCBA -- annual meeting - Kamloops, 1965; F-147-7-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
    - BCCBA -- annual meeting - Salmon Arm, 1965; F-147-7-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
    - BCCBA -- annual meeting - Creston, 1966; F-147-7-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
    - BCCBA -- 6th annual meeting - Vancouver, 1967; F-147-7-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
    - BCCBA -- 8th annual meeting - Salem, Oregon, 1969; F-147-7-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
    - BCCBA -- 9th annual meeting - Vernon, 1970; F-147-7-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
    - BCCBA -- 11th annual meeting - Kelowna, 1972; F-147-7-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 147-15)
- Subject files, 1936 - 2000; F-147-8; 32 cm of textual records 3 photographs
  Series comprises records from various sources on a variety of topics of interest to the BCHPA. Records include annual reports, correspondence, lecture notes, publications, membership lists and other documents.